(Q11（单选）) It's great to see so many members of the Twinning Association here tonight. 很高兴今晚看到这么多友好城市协会（Twinning Association）的成员来到这里。⭐ It's great to see... —— 很高兴看到……｜members of... —— ……成员｜Twinning Association —— 城市友好协会；姊妹城市协会
Since the twinning link between our two towns, Stanthorpe here in England and Malatte in France, was established, the relationship between the towns has gone from strength to strength. 自从我们两个城镇——英国的Stanthorpe和法国的Malatte——建立友好关系以来，两地之间的关系不断加强。⭐ twinning link —— 城市友好关系｜be established —— 被建立｜go from strength to strength —— 不断发展壮大；越来越好
Last month, 25 members of the association from Stanthorpe spent a weekend in Malatte. 上个月，Stanthorpe协会的25名成员在Malatte度过了一个周末。⭐ spend a weekend in... —— 在……度过周末
Our hosts had arranged a great programme. 我们的接待方安排了一个很棒的活动计划。⭐ host —— 接待方；主人｜arrange a programme —— 安排活动计划
We learned how cheese is produced in the region and had the chance to taste the products. 我们了解了当地奶酪的生产过程，并有机会品尝这些产品。⭐ how sth is produced —— 某物如何生产｜have the chance to do sth —— 有机会做某事｜taste the products —— 品尝产品
The theme park trip had to be cancelled, but we all had a great time on the final boat trip down the river – that was the real highlight. 主题公园之旅不得不取消，但我们最后的河上乘船旅行玩得很开心——那才是真正的亮点。⭐ have to be cancelled —— 不得不被取消｜have a great time —— 玩得开心｜boat trip down the river —— 沿河乘船旅行｜highlight —— 亮点
This is a special year for the Association because it's 25 years since we were founded. 今年对协会来说是特殊的一年，因为我们成立已经25年了。⭐ special year —— 特殊的一年｜it's ... years since... —— 自从……已经……年｜be founded —— 成立
In Malatte, they're planning to mark this by building a footbridge in the municipal park. 在Malatte，他们计划通过在市政公园建造一座人行桥来纪念这一周年。⭐ mark sth —— 纪念某事｜by doing sth —— 通过做某事｜footbridge —— 人行桥｜municipal park —— 市政公园
We've been discussing what to do here and we've decided to plant a poplar tree in the museum gardens. 我们一直在讨论这里应该做什么，并决定在博物馆花园里种一棵白杨树。⭐ discuss what to do —— 讨论做什么｜decide to do sth —— 决定做某事｜poplar tree —— 白杨树
We considered buying a garden seat to put there, but the authorities weren't happy with that idea. 我们曾考虑买一个花园座椅放在那里，但相关部门不赞成这个想法。⭐ consider doing sth —— 考虑做某事｜authorities —— 官方部门；管理机构｜be happy with... —— 对……满意
In terms of fundraising to support our activities, we've done very well. 就为支持活动而进行的筹款而言，我们做得非常好。⭐ in terms of... —— 就……而言｜fundraising —— 筹款｜support activities —— 支持活动
Our pancake evening was well attended and made record profits. And everyone enjoyed the demonstration of French cookery, which was nearly as successful. 我们的煎饼晚会参加人数很多，并创造了创纪录的利润。大家也很喜欢法国烹饪展示活动，后者也几乎同样成功。⭐ be well attended —— 出席人数多｜make record profits —— 创造创纪录利润｜demonstration of... —— ……展示｜cookery —— 烹饪
Numbers for our film show were limited because of the venue so we're looking for somewhere bigger next year. 由于场地限制，我们电影放映活动的人数有限，因此明年我们正在寻找更大的地方。⭐ numbers are limited —— 人数有限｜because of the venue —— 因为场地原因｜look for somewhere bigger —— 寻找更大的地方
We're looking forward to welcoming our French visitors here next week, and I know that many of you here will be hosting individuals or families. 我们期待下周欢迎法国访客来到这里，我知道在座很多人会接待个人访客或家庭。⭐ look forward to doing sth —— 期待做某事｜welcome visitors —— 欢迎访客｜host individuals or families —— 接待个人或家庭
The coach from France will arrive at 5 pm on Friday. 来自法国的大巴将在星期五下午5点抵达。⭐ coach —— 长途客车｜arrive at... —— 到达……
Don't try to do too much that first evening as they'll be tired, so have dinner in the house or garden rather than eating out. 第一晚不要安排太多活动，因为他们会很累，所以请在家里或花园吃饭，而不是外出就餐。⭐ that first evening —— 第一个晚上｜rather than doing sth —— 而不是做某事｜eat out —— 外出吃饭
The weather looks as if it'll be OK so you might like to plan a barbecue. 天气看起来不错，所以你们可以考虑安排一次烧烤。⭐ look as if... —— 看起来似乎……｜plan a barbecue —— 安排烧烤
Then the next morning's market day in town, and that's always a good place to stroll round. 第二天早上是镇上的集市日，那一直是散步逛逛的好地方。⭐ market day —— 集市日｜stroll round —— 闲逛
On Saturday evening, we'll all meet up at the football club, where once again we'll have Toby Sharp and his band performing English and Scottish country songs. 星期六晚上，我们将在足球俱乐部集合，届时Toby Sharp和他的乐队会再次表演英格兰和苏格兰乡村歌曲。⭐ meet up —— 集合；见面｜perform songs —— 表演歌曲
Toby will already be well known to many of you as last year he organised our special quiz night and presented the prizes. Toby对很多人来说已经很熟悉了，因为去年他组织了我们的特别问答晚会并颁发了奖品。⭐ be well known to sb —— 为某人所熟知｜quiz night —— 问答比赛晚会｜present prizes —— 颁奖
(Q16（地图）) Now on Sunday, we'll be taking our visitors to Farley House. You may not all be familiar with it, so here's a map to help you. 星期天，我们会带访客去Farley House。你们可能不是所有人都熟悉那里，所以这里有一张地图帮助大家。⭐ be familiar with... —— 熟悉……｜a map to help you —— 帮助定位的地图
You can see the car park at the bottom of the map. There's an excellent farm shop in the grounds where our visitors can buy local produce – it's in the old stables, which is the first building you come to. 你可以看到地图底部的停车场。园区内有一家很棒的农场商店，访客可以买当地产品——它位于旧马厩里，是你进入后看到的第一栋建筑。⭐ at the bottom of the map —— 在地图底部｜in the grounds —— 在园区内｜local produce —— 当地产品｜the first building you come to —— 第一个到达的建筑
They're built round a courtyard, and the shop's in the far corner on the left. 这些建筑围绕一个庭院建造，而商店在左侧最里面的角落。⭐ be built round... —— 围绕……建造｜courtyard —— 庭院｜far corner —— 最里面的角落
There's also a small café on the right as you go in. 进入后右侧还有一家小咖啡馆。⭐ as you go in —— 当你进入时
(Q17) I know that one or two of our visitors may not be all that mobile. 我知道我们的访客中可能有一两位行动不太方便。⭐ not all that... —— 不那么……｜mobile —— 活动方便的
The main entrance to the house has a lot of steps so you might want to use the disabled entry. 房子的主入口有很多台阶，所以你们可能想使用残疾人入口。⭐ main entrance —— 主入口｜disabled entry —— 无障碍入口
This is on the far side of the house from the car park. 这个入口位于房子另一侧，和停车场相对。⭐ the far side of... —— ……另一侧
(Q18) Children will probably be most interested in the adventure playground. 孩子们可能最感兴趣的是冒险游乐场。⭐ be interested in... —— 对……感兴趣
That's at the northern end of the larger lake, in a bend on the path that leads to the lake. 它位于大湖的北端，在通往湖边的小路弯道处。⭐ northern end —— 北端｜in a bend —— 在弯道处｜lead to... —— 通向……
There's lots for children to do there. 那里有很多适合孩子做的活动。 ⭐
(Q19) There are a number of lovely gardens near the house. The kitchen gardens are rectangular and surrounded by a wall. 房子附近还有一些漂亮的花园。厨房花园是矩形的，并且被围墙包围。 ⭐ a number of... —— 许多……｜rectangular —— 矩形的｜be surrounded by... —— 被……围绕
They're to the north-east of the house, quite near the smaller lake. 它们位于房子的东北方，离小湖很近。⭐ north-east of... —— 在……东北方
They're still in use and have a great collection of fruit and vegetables. 它们仍然在使用，并且种植了大量水果和蔬菜。⭐ in use —— 使用中｜a collection of... —— 一系列……
(Q20) The Temple of the Four Winds is a bit more of a walk – but it's worth it. 四风神庙距离稍远一些——但值得一去。⭐ a bit more of a walk —— 需要走更远一点｜be worth it —— 值得
Take the path from the car park and go past the western sides of the stables and the house. 从停车场沿小路走，经过马厩和房子的西侧。⭐ take the path —— 走这条路｜go past —— 经过｜western side —— 西侧
Then when the path forks, take the right-hand path. Go up there with the woods on your left and the temple is right at the end. 然后在道路分叉处走右边的小路。沿着那条路向上走，树林在你的左侧，神庙就在尽头。⭐ path forks —— 道路分叉｜right-hand path —— 右侧道路｜with sth on your left —— 某物在你的左侧｜right at the end —— 就在尽头
There are great views over the whole area. 在那里可以俯瞰整个区域的美景。⭐ views over... —— 俯瞰……的景色